<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on nperumal - blog</title>
    <link>http://nperumal.github.io/categories/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on nperumal - blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 12:10:14 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://nperumal.github.io/categories/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>System Security Design - overview</title>
      <link>http://nperumal.github.io/posts/systemsecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 12:10:14 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nperumal.github.io/posts/systemsecurity/</guid>
      <description>When designing a Software System, ensuring its security is of utmost importance. A security design of any software system should consider securities between
various systems (internal and external), various layers of the same system (from Data layer to view) the system &amp;amp; the world (Actors) During the Software Design phase, Threat Modeling should be employed to recognize any potential internal or external threats. identifies all the threats (internal and external). (This article does not focus on guidance on constructing a threat model for a system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clarity Design System - UX design and development system for all</title>
      <link>http://nperumal.github.io/posts/vmwareclarity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 08:39:46 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nperumal.github.io/posts/vmwareclarity/</guid>
      <description>I came across vmware&amp;rsquo;s Clarity Design System when I was looking to setup a blog (static website) for myself. Being in the Software Development (mostly on the backend development) for a good amount of my professional life, I could put together a website using nodejs or python fairly quickly but that needed a service to host the web server etc. Looking around the web, I decided to go with &amp;lsquo;Hugo&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;GitHub&amp;rsquo; for a free blog host.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An autobiography by chatGPT-3</title>
      <link>http://nperumal.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 09:38:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nperumal.github.io/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>“chatGPT chatGPT chatGPT“ The buzz around the tech world is so noisy that, by now, you probably heard of or played with chatGPT. When I started to learn more about chatGPT and was thinking how chatGPT-3 can help me in my day-to-day life. Well, I am a Software Engineer and hate writing engineering documents. A thought splash in my mind, “Hey, why don’t we ask chatGPT to do the work for me?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
